Guide to the Office of Sponsored Research records, 1942-1996 RG0038
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Office of Sponsored Research records
1942-1996
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
George Washington University. Office of Sponsored Research
RG0038
45.5 Linear Feet
Collection consists of government contract projects with the U.S. Navy, logistics technical project reports, contracting manuals, sponsored research project files from various schools, departments, and programs.
Restrictions on Access
Series 1, 2, 4, and 5 are closed to research for 25 years from date of record creation.
Acquisition Information
Materials acquired through transfers from the Office of Sponsored Research.
Historical or Biographical Note
The Sponsored Research Office is now part of the Associate Vice President for Research & Graduate Studies. The Office of Research Services (ORS) was created to support the efforts of the GW community to generate and manage external awards in support of research, training, instruction, and public service activities. ORS works with investigators in every University component to decipher and adhere to University and sponsor regulations, while reducing time spent on the administrative aspects of sponsored activities. ORS is the University office designated to represent the University in providing the final institutional signature on proposals, in negotiating terms and conditions for grants, contracts, subcontracts, and other award mechanisms, and in dealing with administrative representatives of external sponsors on issues related to sponsored programs.
Collection Scope and Content
The collection consists of government contract projects with the U.S. Navy, logistics technical project reports, contracting manuals, sponsored research project files from various schools, departments, and programs (including the School of Education, School of Engineering, Medical School, National Law Center, Institute for Educational Leadership, Social Research Group, Education Research Project, and logistics), lists of sponsored research awards, Allegany Ballistics Laboratory project files, and reports of the Human Resources Research Organization (HUMRRO). They range in date from 1942 to 1996, and were transferred to the University Archives by the Director of the Department of Sponsored Research. Note: Not all series are processed. Ask staff for assistance.
Collection Organization
Organized into ten series: Government contract projects; Logistics projects reports; Manuals and programs; Project files for schools, departments, programs; Project files for programs and institutes; Lists of sponsored research awards; Alleghany ballistic laboratory project files; Human Resources Research Organization (HUMRRO); Research records; and Photos of the Alleghany research project.
World War, 1939-1945; Washington (D.C.); Logistics; Research; George Washington University. Human Resources Research Office; George Washington University
- Government contract projects, 1951-1958; RG0038 Series 1; 11 Linear feet
  Scope and Contents note
  This series consists of government contract projects with the U.S. Navy. These include reports and contracts with individual shipyards, such as Boston, Charleston, Long Beach, Pearl Harbor, and San Francisco, as well as individual ships in various naval fleets, forces, and naval bases. Their arrangement is predominantly chronological by subject at the beginning and then by subject at the end. The material dates from 1952-1957, and were transferred to the University Archives by the Director of Sponsored Research in 1990.
  - Boston Naval Shipyard, 1952-1957 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Charleston Naval Shipyard, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Long Beach Naval Shipyard, 1954-1957 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Long Beach Naval Shipyard, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Long Beach: Invoices, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Marie Island Naval Shipyard, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Marie Island Naval Shipyard, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Marie Island Naval Shipyard, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Marie Island Naval Shipyard, 1955-1957 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Marie Island: Invoices, 1953-1957 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - New London Submarine Base, 1952-1957 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - New York Naval Shipyard, 1952-1957 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Norfolk Naval Shipyard, 1955-1957 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Norfolk Naval Shipyard, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Norfolk Naval Shipyard, 1952-1953 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Norfolk Naval Shipyard: Service to Fleet Publications, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Norfolk Naval Shipyard Invoices, 1953-1957 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Pearl Harbor Naval Shipyard, 1954-1957 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Pearl Harbor Naval Shipyard, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Pearl Harbor Naval Shipyard, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Pearl Harbor: Invoices Pearl Harbor Submarine Base, 1954-1957 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Pearl Harbor Submarine Base, 1952-1953 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Pearl Harbor Submarine Base: Invoices, undated (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Philadelphia Naval Shipyard, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Portsmouth Naval Shipyard, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    General note
    1952-1953
  - San Francisco Naval Shipyard, 1955-1957 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - San Francisco Naval Shipyard, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - San Francisco Naval Shipyard, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - San Francisco Naval Shipyard, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - San Francisco: Invoices, 1952-1956 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Puget Sound Naval Shipyard, 1953-1957 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Puget Sound Naval Shipyard, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Speed Letters and Communications, 1952-1957 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Divider: Korean Data Collection Plan Ships, 1955-1956 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - USS AJAX, 1952-1958 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    AR6: Repair Ship
  - USS Albuquerque, 1952-1958 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    PF7
  - USS Algol, 1952-1958 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    AKA 54
  - USS Amphion, 1952-1958 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    AR13
  - USS Arcadia, 1952-1958 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    AP23
  - USS Askari, 1955-1958 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    ARL 30
  - USS Atlas, 1955-1958 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    ARL 7
  - USS Badoeing Strait, 1952-1958 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    CVE 116 Carrier
  - USS Barroko, 1952-1958 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    CVE 115
  - USS Bausell, 1952-1958 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    DD 445
  - USS Blenny, 1952-1958 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    SS 324
  - USS Boxer, 1952-1958 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    CVS 21
  - USS Briareus, 1955-1958 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    AR 12
  - USS Bryce Canyon, undated (Box 2, Folder 25)
    AD 36
  - USS Bogara, 1952-1957 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    SS 331
  - USS Cadmus, 1952-1957 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    AR 14: Repair Ship
  - USS Caliente, 1952-1957 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    AO 53
  - USS Cascade, 1952-1957 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    AD 16
  - USS Catamount, 1952-1957 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    LSD 11
  - USS Charr, 1952-1957 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    SS 328
  - USS Colonial, 1952-1957 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    LSD 18
  - USS Comstock, 1952-1957 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    LSD 19
  - USS Delta, 1952-1957 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    AR 9: Tender ship
  - USS Diachenko, 1952-1957 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    APD 123
  - USS Dionysis, 1952-1957 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    AR 21
  - USS Dixie, 1952-1957 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    AD 14
  - USS ElDorado, 1952-1957 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    AGC 11: Amphibious
  - USS Electron, 1952-1957 (Box 2, Folder 39)
    AKS 27
  - USS Endicott, 1952-1957 (Box 2, Folder 40)
    PMS 35
  - USS Essex, 1952-1957 (Box 2, Folder 41)
    CUA 9
  - USS Everglades, 1952-1957 (Box 2, Folder 42)
    AD 24
  - USS Fechteler, 1952-1957 (Box 2, Folder 43)
    PDR 870: Destroyer
  - USS Frontier, 1952-1957 (Box 2, Folder 44)
    AD 25
  - USS Fulton, 1952-1957 (Box 2, Folder 45)
    AS 11
  - USS Grand Canyon, 1952-1957 (Box 2, Folder 46)
    AD 28: Tender ship
  - USS Greenfish, 1955-1957 (Box 2, Folder 47)
    SS 351
  - USS Hamner, 1952-1957 (Box 2, Folder 48)
    DD 718
  - USS Hamul, 1955-1957 (Box 2, Folder 49)
    AD 20
  - USS Helena, 1952-1957 (Box 2, Folder 50)
    California 75
  - USS Hector, 1952-1957 (Box 2, Folder 51)
    AR 7
  - USS Higbee, 1952-1957 (Box 2, Folder 52)
    DDR 806
  - USS Hooper Island, 1952-1957 (Box 2, Folder 53)
    ARG 17
  - USS Horace A. Bois, 1952-1957 (Box 2, Folder 54)
    APD 124
  - USS Howard W. Gilmore, 1952-1957 (Box 2, Folder 55)
    AS 16
  - USS Juneau, 1952-1957 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    SLA 119: Cruiser
  - USS Jason, 1952-1957 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    AR 1
  - USS Juniper, undated (Box 3, Folder 3)
    AUS 8
  - USS Kermit Roosevelt, 1952-1957 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    ARG 16: Repair Ship
  - USS Laertes, 1952-1957 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    AR 20: Repair Ship
  - USS Los Angeles, 1952-1957 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    CA 135
  - USS Manchester, 1952-1957 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    CC 83
  - USS Lozon, 1952-1957 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    ARG 2
  - USS Markab, 1952-1957 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    AD 21
  - USS Marsh, 1952-1957 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    DE 699
  - USS Missouri, 1952-1957 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    BB 63
  - USS Mountraid, 1952-1957 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    APA 213
  - USS Mt Mckinly, 1952-1957 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    AGC 7
  - USS Nereus, 1952-1957 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    AS 17: Tender ship
  - USS New Jersey, 1952-1957 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    BB 62
  - USS Noble, 1952-1957 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    APA 218
  - USS Okanogan, 1952-1957 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    APA 220: Amphibious
  - USS Orion, 1952-1957 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    AS 18
  - USS Perch, 1952-1957 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    ASSP 313: Submarine
  - USS Philippine Sea, 1955-1956 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    CVA 47
  - USS Pickaway, 1952-1957 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    APA 222
  - USS Picherel, 1952-1957 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    SS 524
  - USS Piedmont, 1952-1957 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    AD 17
  - USS Platte, 1952-1957 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    AO 24
  - USS Pomodon, 1955-1956 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    SS 486
  - USS Prairie, 1952-1957 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    AD 15
  - USS Proton, 1952-1957 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    ADS 20
  - USS Radford, 1952-1957 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    DDE 446: Destroyer
  - USS Redfish, 1952-1957 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    SS 395
  - USS Richard B. Anderson, 1952-1957 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    DD 786
  - USS Rochester, 1952-1957 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    CA 124
  - USS Pomulus, 1952-1957 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    ARL 22
  - USS Rupertus, 1952-1957 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    DD 851
  - USS Satyr, 1952-1957 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    ARL 23: Repair Ship
  - USS Segundo, 1952-1957 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    SS 398
  - USS Shenadoah, 1952-1957 (Box 3, Folder 36)
    AD 26
  - USS Sierra, 1952-1957 (Box 3, Folder 37)
    AD 18
  - USS Southerland, 1952-1957 (Box 3, Folder 38)
    DDR 743
  - USS Spangler, 1952-1957 (Box 3, Folder 39)
    DE 696
  - USS Sperry, 1952-1957 (Box 3, Folder 40)
    AS 12
  - USS Spinx, 1952-1957 (Box 3, Folder 41)
    ARL 24
  - USS Spinax, 1952-1957 (Box 3, Folder 42)
    SSR 489
  - USS Sterlet, 1952-1957 (Box 3, Folder 43)
    SS 392
  - USS Thompson, 1952-1957 (Box 3, Folder 44)
    DMS 38
  - USS Tidewater, 1952-1957 (Box 3, Folder 45)
    AD 31
  - USS Tiru, 1952-1957 (Box 3, Folder 46)
    SS 416
  - USS Toledo, 1952-1958 (Box 3, Folder 47)
    CA 133
  - USS Tutuila, 1952-1957 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - USS Valley Forge, 1952-1957 (Box 3, Folder 49)
    CVS 45: Cruiser
  - USS Vulcan, 1952-1957 (Box 3, Folder 50)
    AR 5
  - USS Waller, 1952-1957 (Box 3, Folder 51)
    DDE 466: Destroyer
  - USS Whiteside, 1952-1957 (Box 3, Folder 52)
    AKA 90
  - USS Winston, 1952-1957 (Box 3, Folder 53)
    AKA 94
  - USS Wisconsin, 1952-1957 (Box 3, Folder 54)
    BB 64
  - USS Yancey, 1952-1957 (Box 3, Folder 55)
    AKA 9: Amphibious
  - USS Yellowstone, 1952-1957 (Box 3, Folder 56)
    AD 27
  - USS Yorktown, 1952-1957 (Box 3, Folder 57)
    CVA 10
  - USS Yosemite, 1952-1957 (Box 3, Folder 58)
    AD 19
  - Divider: Korean Data Collection Plan Ships, 1952-1954 (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - General Correspondence, 1952-1954 (Box 3, Folder 60)
    Sample Ships, etc
  - Korean Data Collection Plan Research Papers, undated (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - Divider: Type Commanders, 1955-1957 (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - Commander in Chief Atlantic Fleet, 1955-1957 (Box 3, Folder 63)
    CIndianaCLouisianaNTFLT
  - Commander in Chief Pacific Fleet, 1955-1957 (Box 3, Folder 64)
  - Commander Air Force: Pacific Fleet, 1955-1957 (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - Commander Amphibious Force: Pacific Fleet, 1955-1957 (Box 3, Folder 66)
  - Commander Battleship: Cruiser Force Atlantic Fleet, 1955-1957 (Box 3, Folder 67)
  - Commander Cruiser: Destroyer Force Pacific Fleet, 1955-1957 (Box 3, Folder 68)
  - Commander Destroyer Force: Atlantic Fleet, 1955-1957 (Box 3, Folder 69)
  - Commander Mine Force: Pacific Fleet, 1955-1957 (Box 3, Folder 70)
  - Commander Naval Forces: Philippines, 1955-1957 (Box 3, Folder 71)
    Empty folder
  - Commander Service Squadron Three: Pacific Fleet, 1955-1957 (Box 3, Folder 72)
  - Commander Submarine Flotilla One: Pacific, 1955-1957 (Box 3, Folder 73)
    Comsubflot 1
  - Commander Submarine: Atlantic Fleet, 1952-1957 (Box 3, Folder 74)
  - Commander Submarine force: Pacific Fleet, 1955-1957 (Box 3, Folder 75)
    COMSUBPAC
  - Commander Sub Group Two: Naval Base at Philadelphia, PA, 1955-1957 (Box 3, Folder 76)
  - Eastern Pacific Amphibious Group, 1955-1957 (Box 3, Folder 77)
    EASTPALPHIB SGROUP
  - Divider: Type Commanders, 1952-1954 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Commander Service Force: Pacific Fleet, 1952-1954 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    COMSERVPC
  - Commander-in-Chief Atlantic Fleet, 1952-1954 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Commander-in-Chief Pacific Fleet, 1952-1954 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Commander Air Force: Pacific Fleet, 1952-1954 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Commander Amphibious Force: Pacific Fleet, 1952-1954 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    COMPHIBPAC
  - Commander Battleship-Cruiser Force: Atlantic Fleet, 1952-1954 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Commander Cruiser Force: Atlantic Fleet, 1952-1954 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Commander Cruiser-Destroyer Force: Pacific Fleet, 1952-1954 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Commander Destroyer Force Atlantic Fleet, 1952-1954 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Commander Mine Force: Pacific Fleet, 1952-1954 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Commander Naval Forces: Far East, 1952-1954 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Commander Naval Forces: Philippines, 1952-1954 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Commander Service Force: Atlantic Fleet, 1952-1954 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Commander Service Squadron Three: Pacific Fleet, 1952-1954 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Commander Submarine Force: Pacific Fleet, 1952-1954 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Pacific Fleet Evaluation Group, 1952-1954 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    PACFLTEVALGRU
  - Divider: Korean Data Collection Plan General Correspondence and Memos, 1955-1957 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Korean Data Collection Plan Progress and Status Reports, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    General Correspondence
  - General Correspondence, 1956-1957 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Shipmits Received: Memos, 1955-1957 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Busanda Instruction Memoranda, 1957-1958 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Memoranda [1/2], 1956 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Memoranda [2/2], 1955 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Korean War Patrols Reports, undated (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Divider: Naval Centers, Depots, Station AIMs, IMs, 1955-1956 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Atlantic Reserve Fleet, 1955-1957 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Pacific Reserve Fleet, 1955-1957 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Industrial Manager: 5th Naval District, 1955-1957 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Industrial Manager: 6th Naval Division, 1955-1957 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Assistant Industrial Manager: Naval Station, San Diego, 1955-1957 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Assistant Industrial Manager: 11 Naval District, Long Beach, California, 1955-1957 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Industrial Manager: 13 Naval District, Bremerton, Washington, 1955-1957 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Industrial Manager: 15 Naval District, Fort Amador, 1955-1957 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Assistant Industrial Manager, Astonia, Oregon, 1955-1957 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Assistant Industrial Manager: 6th Naval District, Jacksonville, Florida, 1955-1957 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Assistant Industrial Manager: 12th Naval District, San Francisco, 1955-1957 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Alameda Naval Air Station, 1956-1957 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Assistant Industrial Manager: Seattle, Washington, 1955-1957 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Naval Repair Facility: San Diego, 1955-1957 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Naval Station: Guantanamo Bay, 1955-1957 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Naval Station: Key West, 1955-1957 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Naval Station: Subic Bay, Philippine Islands, 1955-1957 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Naval Supply Center: Norfolk, Virginia, 1955-1957 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Naval Supply Depot: Bayonne, New Jersey, 1955-1957 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Naval Supply Depot: Ship Repair Facility at Guam, Marianas, 1955-1957 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Naval Supply Depot: San Diego, California [1/2], 1955-1957 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Naval Supply Depot: San Pedro, California [2/2], 1955-1957 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Fleet Activities, Sasebo, 1955-1957 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Fleet Air Station: Norfolk, Virginia, 1955-1957 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Naval Air Station: San Diego, 1955-1957 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Fleet Activities: Yokosuka, 1955-1957 (Box 4, Folder 52)
    Navy Number 3923
  - Divider: Private Shipyards, 1955-1956 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Bay City Electric Work, 1955-1957 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Bethlehem Pacific Coast Steel Corporation, 1955-1957 (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - California Electronic Work, 1955-1957 (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Campbell Machine Company: San Diego, California, 1955-1957 (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Coastal Marine Repair Company: San Francisco, California, 1955-1956 (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Chaffee Machine Work, 1955-1957 (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - Colberg Boak Work, 1955-1957 (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - Columbia Machine Company, 1955-1957 (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - Craig Shipbuilding Company, 1955-1957 (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - ETS: Hokin and Galvan, 1955-1957 (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - Fellows and Stewart, 1955-1957 (Box 4, Folder 64)
  - Forster Shipbuilding Company, 1955-1957 (Box 4, Folder 65)
  - Harbor Boat building Company, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 66)
  - John's Boat Shop, 1955-1957 (Box 4, Folder 67)
  - Long Beach Marine Repair Company, 1955-1957 (Box 4, Folder 68)
  - Martin Olich Shipbuilding Company, 1955-1957 (Box 4, Folder 69)
  - Misc Private Shipyards, 1956-1957 (Box 4, Folder 70)
  - Moore Dry Dock Company, 1955-1957 (Box 4, Folder 71)
  - National Steel and Shipbuilding Company, 1955-1957 (Box 4, Folder 72)
  - Pacific Ship Repair, Inc, 1955-1957 (Box 4, Folder 73)
  - San Diego Marine Construction Company, 1955-1957 (Box 4, Folder 74)
  - Todd Shipyards Corporation, 1955-1957 (Box 4, Folder 75)
  - Wagner and Niehaus, 1955-1957 (Box 4, Folder 76)
  - Wilmington Welding and Boiler Work, 1955-1957 (Box 4, Folder 77)
  - Triple A Machine Shop: San Francisco, California, 1955-1957 (Box 4, Folder 78)
  - Korean Data Collection Plan: General Correspondence, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 79)
  - Korean Data Collection Plan: General Correspondence and Memos, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 80)
  - Divider: Naval Centers, Depots, and Stations, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 81)
    AIM, IMs
  - Atlantic Reserve Fleet, 1953-1954 (Box 4, Folder 82)
  - Pacific Reserve Fleet, 1953-1954 (Box 4, Folder 83)
  - Industrial Manager: 15th Naval District, Canal Zone, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 84)
  - Industrial Manager: 11th Naval District, Long Beach, California, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 85)
  - Asst Industrial Manag- 12th Naval District, San Francisco, California, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 86)
  - Asst Industrial Manag: Naval Station, San Diego, California, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 87)
  - Naval Station: Argentina, Newfoundland, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 88)
    Navy 103
  - Naval Station: Guantanamo Bay, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 89)
  - Naval Station: Key West, Florida, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 90)
  - U S Naval Station: San Diego, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 91)
  - Naval Station: Susbic Bay, Philippines, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 92)
  - Naval Supply Depot: Bayonne, New Jersey, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 93)
  - Naval Supply Depot: San Pedro, California, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 94)
  - Naval Supply Center: Oakland, California, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 95)
  - Naval Repair Facility: San Diego, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 96)
  - Fleet Activities: Sasebo, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 97)
  - Fleet Activities: Yokosuka, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 98)
  - Fleet Air Station: Norfolk Fleet Aviation Accounting Office, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 99)
    ATLouisianaNTIC
  - Naval Air Station: San Diego Fleet Aviation Accounting Office, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 100)
    PACIFIC
  - Divider: Private Shipyards, 1953-1954 (Box 4, Folder 101)
  - Bethlehem Pacific Coast Steel Corporation: San Francisco, California, 1953-1954 (Box 4, Folder 102)
  - Craig Ship Building Company: Long Beach, California, 1953-1954 (Box 4, Folder 103)
  - Fellows and Steward: San Pedro, California, 1953-1954 (Box 4, Folder 104)
  - Forster Shipbuilding Company: San Pedro, California, 1953-1954 (Box 4, Folder 105)
  - Harbor Boat Building Company: Los Angeles Harbor, California, 1953-1954 (Box 4, Folder 106)
  - Long Beach Marine Repair Company, 1953-1954 (Box 4, Folder 107)
  - Plant Shipyard Corporation: Alameda, California, 1953-1954 (Box 4, Folder 108)
  - Todd Shipyards Corporation: San Pedro, California, 1953-1954 (Box 4, Folder 109)
  - Triple A Machine Shop: San Francisco, California, 1953-1954 (Box 4, Folder 110)
  - Wilmington Welding and Boiler Works: Wilmington, California, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 111)
  - Divider: Korean Data Collection Plan General Correspondence, 1952-1953 (Box 4, Folder 112)
  - Authorization and Instructions: Correspondence, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 113)
  - Daily Shipment Reports, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 114)
  - Deck Logs, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 115)
  - Availabilities, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 116)
  - In Storage Shipments, 1952-1953 (Box 4, Folder 117)
  - Memoranda Shipments, 1952-1953 (Box 4, Folder 118)
  - Korean Data Collection Plan General Correspondence, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 119)
  - Memoranda Processing Procedures, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 120)
  - Korean Data Collection Plan General Correspondence, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 121)
  - Naval Material Accounting Procedure Course, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 122)
  - Minutes of Korean Data Collection Plan Meetings, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 123)
    Extra Copies
  - Divider: Naval Centers, Depots, Station AIMS, IMs Assistant Industrial Manager, 1952-1953 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    6th Naval District, Jacksonville, Florida
  - Industrial Manager: 8th Naval District, New Orleans, Louisiana, 1952-1953 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Industrial Manager: 11th Naval District, Long Beach, California, 1952-1953 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Assistant Industrial Manager: 12th Naval District, San Francisco, California, 1952-1953 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Industrial Manager: 15th Naval District, Balboa, Canal Zone, 1952-1953 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Asst Industrial Manager: Orange, Texas, 1952-1953 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Asst Industrial Manager: Naval Station, San Diego, California, 1952-1953 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Asst Industrial Manager: Seattle, Washington, 1952-1953 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Naval Station: Argentina, New Foundland, 1952-1953 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Naval Supply Depot: Bayonne, New Jersey, 1952-1953 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Naval Station: Guantanamo Bay, 1952-1953 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Naval Station: Key West, Florida, 1952-1953 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Naval Supply Depot: Naval Base and Ship Repair Facility, 1952-1953 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    Guam, Marianas
  - Naval Supply Depot: New Port, Rhode Island, 1952-1953 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Naval Supply Depot: San Diego, California, 1952-1953 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Naval Supply Depot: San Pedro, California, 1953 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Naval Supply Center: Norfolk, Virginia, 1952-1953 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Naval Supply Center: Oakland, California, 1952-1953 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Fleet Air Station: Norfolk Fleet Aviation Accounting Office, 1952-1953 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    Atlantic